ad-center.com 2019-05-31

# Ad Center - Privacy

This policy was last updated May 29th 2018

This Privacy Policy covers [www.ad-center.com](https://www.ad-center.com/)

Ad-Center.com is committed to maintaining the privacy of personal & business information that you provide to us when using our online affiliate services. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat the information we receive when you transmit data to any machine owned by Ad-Center.

Ad-Center complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Ad-Center has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement.

Ad-Center in it's best efforts complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. Please [click here](https://www.ad-center.com/GDPR) for more information regarding Ad-Center's EU Privacy GDPR readiness program.

Information Collection & Use

1\. Web Form Information

When you submit information to ad-center to collect a payment or open an affiliate account, we may collect personally identifiable information from you that may include your name, address, email address, credit card number and bank account details. We do not knowingly collect personal information from persons under the age of eighteen. 

2\. Website Usage Information

We automatically collect IP addresses and website usage information from you when you access any of our online services. This information helps us evaluate how our visitors and program affiliates use and navigate our website on an aggregate basis, including, but not limited to, the number and frequency of visitors and subscribers to each web page and the length of their visits. 

3\. How We Use Information Collected

We may use information in the following ways: 

  1. To perform the actions for which you specifically provided the information (for example, enabling us to process, validate, and verify your account and/or payouts accrued).
  2. To register you as an affiliate and establish an account for you.
  3. To send you email notifications about our new or existing ad-center products and services, special marketing promotions, or to otherwise contact you.
  4. To enhance existing features or develop new feature products and services.
  5. To provide advertisers and other third parties with aggregate information about our user base and usage patterns.
  6. To allow us to personalize the content and advertising that you and others see based on personal characteristics or preferences.

Except as specifically set forth in this Privacy Policy, we will not share, sell, rent, or trade your personally identifiable information with any entity outside of ad-center for promotional purposes. We may disclose and use personally identifiable information in special circumstances where it is necessary to enforce our service agreements or terms of use (for example, to protect our intellectual property rights). We may also disclose or use your personal information when we, in good faith, believe that the law may require us to do so. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website. We may disclose your information in response to valid legal process (e.g. subpoenas, search warrants and court orders or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend legal claims) without notice to you, if so prohibited by court order or law. 

4\. Newsletters

If you are subscribed to our affiliate newsletter, we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, you can unsubscribe by clicking "unsubscribe" within the email at any time. 

5\. Updating Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire to be a part of our affiliate program, you may correct, update, amend, or delete it by logging into My Account, Account Settings, or request the information be corrected through our “Contact Us” page or by contacting us directly using our toll-free client support services line listed below. We will respond to your request within 3 business days. 

6\. Agents/Service Providers

We use other third parties such as a database backup provider to protect our data, a fraud prevention service, and an email service provider to send out emails on our behalf. When you sign up for these services, we will share your personal information as necessary for the third party to provide that service. 

7\. Cookies

We define a cookie as any string of data that is automatically stored on your computer upon access to our online services. Ad-Center employs cookies to assign temporary identification numbers to machines that access our web servers. This information enables us to deliver faster service to our subscribers, prevent Denial of Service attacks on our systems, detect and prevent fraudulent transactions, and assist with awarding proper sales credit to our partners. All Ad-Center cookies are 1) of limited duration, 2) less than 5KB in length, 3) only visible to ad-center web servers, and 4) devoid of any personally identifiable information.

Third parties also use cookies and other tracking technologies on our site, of which data is only collected in the aggregate. 

8\. Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as your banking wire transfer information, or email address) on our registration form, we encrypt that information using SSL. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure -we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information; we cannot guarantee its absolute security. The personally identifiable information we collect about you is stored in limited access servers. We maintain safeguards to protect the security of these servers and your personally identifiable information. We retain personally identifiable information only as long as you continue to continue your affiliation with ad-center.com. 

9\. Links to Other Sites

If you click on a link to a third party site you will leave our site and go to the site you selected. Because we cannot control the activities of third parties, we cannot accept responsibility for any use of your personally identifiable information by such third parties, and we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy practices as us. We encourage you to review the privacy statements of any other service provider from whom you request services. 

10\. Changes in this Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on your Account Home page. 

11\. Comments and Questions

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, you may contact us by submitting your inquiry to our [Affiliate Support Services ](https://www.ad-center.com/contact)
